<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accelerate &amp;amp; Achieve Your Product Vision on JetThoghts Demo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accelerate &amp;amp; Achieve Your Product Vision on JetThoghts Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 23:31:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>See How JetThoughts Helped Agent Inbox Go From Idea to Software in 60 Days</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/agent-inbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/agent-inbox/</guid>
      <description>Agent Inbox is an industry-leading real estate messaging platform that leverages Multiple Listing Services (MLS) data to help centralize &amp;amp; streamline deal-making for realtors.&#xA;Agent Inbox envisioned an idea to create a competitive software product to disrupt real estate communication.&#xA;To attract investors and customers as quickly as possible, Agent Inbox desired to develop a Minimal Viable Product (MVP) that could be used as a foundation for additional development.&#xA;They initially reached out to JetThoughts to make their product idea a reality and help build the right internal development team for long-term success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How JetThoughts Helped Stabilize Open Apply’s Code &amp; Transform Their Product’s UX</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/open-apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/open-apply/</guid>
      <description>Client Overview OpenApply is a fast-growing software platform to help simplify the admissions and enrollment processes for applicants around the world with a paperless, integrated online experience.&#xA;They initially reached out to JetThoughts to help stop regressions, revamp the user experience, scale feature development, and streamline internal development processes.&#xA;Vision Open Apply envisioned an upgrade of their technology operations from end-to-end: fewer bugs, better UX/UI, faster development, and higher-quality releases..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How JetThoughts Helped Mobile Coach Launch a Game-Changing Product Feature &amp; Scale Their Development Team</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/mobile-coach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/mobile-coach/</guid>
      <description>Client Overview Mobile Coach is a chatbot platform that&amp;rsquo;s trying to change how enterprises influence employee engagement, learning, customer service, sales performance, and overall behavior change.&#xA;They initially reached out to JetThoughts to help support and build new features for a group of internal products related to the chatbot platform while eventually helping to scale their R&amp;amp;D team.&#xA;Vision Mobile Coach envisioned an enterprise-level authoring platform which would allow larger customers to setup complicated chatbot workflows with multiple channels, multi-language compatibility, and seamless back-office integrations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Software Quality Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/automate-product-qa-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/automate-product-qa-testing/</guid>
      <description>The problem As a software product grows larger and older, it becomes harder to build upon, upgrade, and optimize. Over time, it can be difficult to simply maintain a codebase without new issues or inefficiencies emerging.&#xA;Without an effective system for product testing as software development scales, companies risk losing control over product performance, stability, and engineering speed.&#xA;How we solve it To enable faster product development while eliminating the risks of costly mistakes, companies need access to a reliable product testing &amp;amp; QA resource that can ensure quality at any scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate The Path To Revenue Without Going Broke</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/startup-mvp-prototyping-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/startup-mvp-prototyping-development/</guid>
      <description>The problem With a lot of luck, startups can identify a market opportunity, understand the right product to build, and secure funding to develop it on a first attempt. Oftentimes though, this early-stage journey from idea &amp;amp; validation to funding &amp;amp; development is long, difficult, and expensive.&#xA;Before it makes sense to realistically spend the time &amp;amp; money building a full software product, startups need a way to align founders, engineers, customers, and investors around a common vision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access Top-tier Software Development Talent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/talent-recruiting-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/talent-recruiting-training/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become Our Junior Ruby On Rails Developer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/careers/junior-ruby-on-rails-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/careers/junior-ruby-on-rails-developer/</guid>
      <description>Opportunity details We are looking for a result-oriented and self-directed person passionate about becoming an effective Ruby on Rails developer.&#xA;We will provide a top-tier training program and help you level up your skills as a software development professional while giving you the opportunity to contribute to real world projects.&#xA;Responsibilities Help maintain a large-scale Ruby on Rails application Help upgrade and test a large-scale Ruby on Rails application Refactor existing code following the TDD principles Pair programming with Developers Code review pull request Candidate Qualifications Experience with the Ruby language and the Ruby on Rails framework.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge The Gap And Build Products Faster</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/fractional-product-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/fractional-product-management/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Better Products And Increase Engineering Manpower</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/empower-existing-engineering-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/empower-existing-engineering-team/</guid>
      <description>The problem Even talented engineering teams can become overwhelmed by customer complaints, technical issues, or aggressive deadlines.&#xA;When a core development team is rushed or overworked, companies risk losing control over the quality of their product, overlooking critical software errors, &amp;amp; missing key deadlines.&#xA;How we solve it The easiest &amp;amp; fastest way to grow software development capacity is by using a trusted technology partner that can deploy pre-trained developers on-demand without the need for additional supervision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Better Software At Half The Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/accelerate-development-maximize-capacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/accelerate-development-maximize-capacity/</guid>
      <description>The problem Software development is a fragile balancing act between speed &amp;amp; quality, which can be difficult to achieve with limited resources or tight deadlines. The longer it takes for a software to be built, the more expensive it can become.&#xA;While any team can build a high-quality product with enough time, very few can deliver high-quality software releases at a competitive speed.&#xA;How we solve it The fastest way to expand software engineering capacity is by using a trusted technology partner that can deploy pre-trained developers on-demand at any scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build High-Quality Tech At A Fraction Of The Cost</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/app-web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/app-web-development/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Software Faster While Ensuring Performance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/software-qa-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/software-qa-cat/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fractional CTOs For Maximum Efficiency</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/fractional-cto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/fractional-cto/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implement The Best Practices For Your Project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/salvage-existing-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/salvage-existing-project/</guid>
      <description>The problem Software is rarely developed perfectly on the first try and usually requires dedicated supervision and testing to prevent critical mistakes.&#xA;However, software products often get handled by multiple people, teams, and leaders over time, which can make it difficult to maintain control over the product. Without good development best practices &amp;amp; clear product documentation, codebases can become impossible to use without consultants or additional technical resources. Many startups fail because they’re unable to continue with the product they have.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Receive Access To Pre-trained Developers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/outsourced-developer-staffing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/outsourced-developer-staffing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How JetThoughts Helped Corsis Transform a Legacy Software Project &amp; Gain Control Over a Complex Codebase</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/see-how-jetthoughts-helped-corsis-transform-a-legacy-software-project-gain-control-over-a-complex-codebase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/see-how-jetthoughts-helped-corsis-transform-a-legacy-software-project-gain-control-over-a-complex-codebase/</guid>
      <description>Corsis is a technology advisory services firm that include consultant-led, self-administered evaluations of a company&amp;rsquo;s adherence to industry best practices.&#xA;Corsis envisioned a transformation of their software project from a complex legacy codebase in need of improvements to a high-quality product that&amp;rsquo;s easier to support.&#xA;In addition, Corsis knew they were in need of more experienced technical resources and desired to evolve their internal development processes to meet industry best practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How JetThoughts Helped LimeLeads Transform a Legacy Codebase &amp; Stabilize the Product for Long-Term Performance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/see-how-jetthoughts-helped-limeleads-transform-a-legacy-codebase-stabilize-the-product-for-long-term-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/see-how-jetthoughts-helped-limeleads-transform-a-legacy-codebase-stabilize-the-product-for-long-term-performance/</guid>
      <description>Client Overview LimeLeads is a searchable B2B database software that provides access to high-quality sales &amp;amp; marketing data with a do-it-yourself user experience and real-time validation.&#xA;They initially reached out to JetThoughts to augment their on-site product development team to help increase the velocity of feature development and bug-fixing at minimal financial cost.&#xA;Vision LimeLeads envisioned a complete transformation of their software product, which was built on an out-of-date codebase years ago by the original founder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See How JetThoughts Helped OrchestrateCS Go From an Idea to Software in Just 60 Days</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/see-how-jetthoughts-helped-orchestratecs-go-from-an-idea-to-software-in-just-60-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/see-how-jetthoughts-helped-orchestratecs-go-from-an-idea-to-software-in-just-60-days/</guid>
      <description>Client Overview OrchestrateCS is a startup building software to help unify, simplify, and standardize both people and compliance operations.&#xA;They initially reached out to JetThoughts to help them go from zero to revenue by making their first product idea a reality.&#xA;Vision OrchestrateCS envisioned a new software idea from scratch to pursue a new business opportunity that had emerged in their industry.&#xA;Given the time-sensitive nature of this project, OrchestrateCS desired to develop a Minimal Viable Product (MVP) and go-to-market as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Bridge The Gap Between Software &amp;amp; IT Operations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/emergency-cto-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/emergency-cto-leadership/</guid>
      <description>The problem Live technology without technical supervision is a risky situation that can become expensive.&#xA;IT &amp;amp; software products need constant supervision from someone with the knowledge to reduce errors, fix problems, &amp;amp; prevent downtime. When a company loses technical leadership, it also loses any visibility into IT performance, security, and stability.&#xA;How we solve it To maintain visibility, accountability, and control over technology outcomes when a critical team member leaves, companies need on-demand access to technical leadership to help keep the status quo for IT intact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Offer A Position For Senior Ruby On Rails Developer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/careers/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/careers/senior-ruby-on-rails-developer/</guid>
      <description>Opportunity details We are looking for a result-oriented and self-directed person aimed at getting the work done in the most efficient way possible with 5+ years of working with Ruby on Rails.&#xA;We will help you be hired directly by an American Product company/startup, and communicate personally with Stakeholders/Product Owners from the client&amp;rsquo;s side.&#xA;With us, you&amp;rsquo;ll choose your own schedule and work from anywhere you want. Moreover, JetThoughts takes care of all the overhead, while you focus only on successful engagements while getting paid on time at the rate you decide for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us And Take Your Career To The Next Level</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/careers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn More About Us and Our Story JetThoughts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimize &amp;amp; Empower Products at Any Stage JetThoughts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Offer Solutions to Companies&amp;#039; Software Development JetThoughts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/use-cases/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We&amp;#039;ve Delivered Positive Outcomes For Clients</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/clients/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get In Touch with One of Our Experts JetThoughts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Visitor&amp;#039;s Privacy Is One Of Our Main Priorities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>At Jet Thoughts, accessible from https://www.jetthoughts.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Jet Thoughts and how we use it.&#xA;If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.&#xA;General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)&#xA;We are a Data Controller of your information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Receive Technical Strategies with Free Consultation JetThoughts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/free-consultation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/free-consultation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
